"quiz_content":
  "question_1":
    "question": "Do you remember a time in your life when you learned a new motor
    skill? (It could be a new gymnastics routine, a new karate move, a new yoga move,
    etc.)."
    "A":
      "answer": "YES"
      "explanation": "You are a brain changer! You use all of your brain and it is
      constantly learning new things to accommodate new capacities. Learning and
      mastering a new skill modifies the brain."
    "B":
      "answer": "NO"
      "explanation": "Hey, you're selling yourself short, You use all of your brain and
       it is constantly learning new things to accommodate new capacities. The brain is
       constantly working, so you have to work it! Your brain is constantly incorporating
       new information."
  "question_2":
    "question": "When faced with a decision, problem, or roadblock, do you rely on
    internal (your brain, knowledge, instinct, passion) or external (other people,
    internet, etc) factors to guide your decision:"
    "A":
      "answer": "External – I value other people's opinions because I appreciate their
      wisdom and insight."
      "explanation": "You expand your brain based off of guidance from other people.
      Trust in a mentor's guidance is integral for building ourselves, but remember to
      trust your own instincts and wherever your brain may lead you!"
    "B":
      "answer": "Internal – I trust myself, instinct, and my passions."
      "explanation": "You trust your instincts and where your brain leads you! This is
      a true strength, but external guidance is also integral to self-development – so
      listen to others– it expands your brain."
  "question_3":
    "question": "Are you the type of person who is at peace when:"
    "A":
      "answer": "Roaming the earth, quiet with my thoughts, and using nature to gain
      insight into who I am as a person (in this life or the last)."
      "explanation": "You have nature on the brain!  The sounds, smells, and
      predictability of nature stimulate multiple senses and give your brain a break from
      the screens that are constantly in front of us! Brain research shows that your
      brain on nature might help you fight stress. Nature's not just pretty, it's great
      for your growth."
    "B":
      "answer": "In front of my computer, connecting with tons of people on Twitter and
      Facebook, while listening to music (which I certainly want to either produce or
      write)."
      "explanation": "You are a media multi-tasker! You love having your fingers on
      everything tech,! You have an ability to take on and process massive amounts of
      information. Just remember to unplug so you and your have time to unwind and
      re-charge!"
  "question_4":
      "question": "Do you try to ‘see' and ‘find' an alternate solution? When confronted
      with a problem in or out of the workplace, do you:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Find a solution directly related to the issue at hand?"
        "explanation": "You think in a linear sequential way! Once you learn a skill or
        task, that's how you know it and apply it. Any other way and no thanks! Just
        remember other skill sets can amplify your problem-solving abilities!"
      "B":
        "answer": "Use abilities you've learned from other skill-sets to help you solve the
        issue at hand?"
        "explanation": "You use information interchangeably! Your brain is able to use
        information you have learned for one reason and apply it to another!"
  "question_5":
      "question": "This one may seem basic, but have you either taught yourself a new
      language or have
                   you learned one through school?"
      "A":
        "answer": "Yes. I dig languages."
        "explanation": "Learning and mastering a new language modifies the brain! Watch a
         movie in another language, travel or listen to your grandmother speak in her
         native tongue – it grows your brain!"
      "B":
        "answer": "No. They say I suck at it."
        "explanation": "Hey, you're not that bad at languages! Learning a language helps
        keep your brain healthy and you don't need to be fluent, just try it. Also, don't
        forget – texting is a new type of language, as is coding. So, if you've taken
        computer science – that counts as a new language and is helping grow your brain!"
  "question_6":
      "question": "This question is central to who you are: when faced with negative feed
      back, do you:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Dwell on the negative and use it as motivation?"
        "explanation": "You are a self-regulator! You process the negative, filter it, and
        use it as motivation to improve your performance. You use negative information like
        a tool-kit and grow from it. Keep up the good work!"
      "B":
        "answer": "Block the negative and instead focus on the positive?"
        "explanation": "Wow! You completely ignore negative feedback that could
        detrimentally affect your motivation and progression in life/work. You are likely
        internally motivated and internalize factors that you yourself decide are
        meaningful to your development in life/work. Watch out world, here you come!"
  "question_7":
      "question": "Ok, this is about how your brain sees: In real life or a video game,
      do you:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Learn outdoor/indoor spaces relatively easily (e.g. you do not need
        google maps to tell you where to go, you know exactly where to go)."
        "explanation": "You are a space navigator! No matter what, you can figure out where
        you are and where to go. There are certain structures in our brains that help us
        navigate. For example, people can learn to navigate and the more they learn how to
        navigate complex spaces, the more the hippocampus grows!"
      "B":
        "answer": "Have no idea where you are going. You can't even navigate out of a
        cardboard box without your phone!"
        "explanation": "If you know this is not your strong suit, your brain can easily
        help you improve this skill! All you have to do is find your way without relying on
        your phone. Your brain can build up your navigational knowledge! Literally,
        portions of your hippocampus plump up like a jacked bicep!"
  "question_8":
      "question": "Learning new characters requires a learning ability to link a label
      (e.g. a name) to an image (e.g. a face). Whether in real life or a video game, do
      you:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Learn new names and faces/objects/beings easily (this can be memorizing
        names and dates for a history class, or even types of birds or cars for fun)."
        "explanation": "You have perceptronic ability! You can distinguish one thing from
        another and incorporate new details. Perceptual expertise can take many forms and
        requires an ability to process fine-grained details – details such as
        differentiating one type of bird or car from another. "
      "B":
        "answer": "Have a lot of trouble learning new names and faces/objects/beings for
        video games or in real life (or for memorizing names and dates in a history class)."
        "explanation": "You are likely a big picture person. You read the gist of a room or
        a scene in the blink of an eye! These skills come in handy in all aspects of
        everyday life! Remember that as much as you may not like fine-grained details, your
        brain likes new things and learning to appreciate details can give your brain a new
        way to learn!"
  "question_9":
      "question": "Have you been given the advice to not let fear dictate your life? Be
      honest with yourself, when faced with a major life decision, do you:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Consider fear as a major factor in your decision process?"
        "explanation": "You are an emotive logician! Using emotion can be a great strategy
        to amplify your decision making process and your logical choices. You feel things
        AND you know at the same time you are heading in the right direction."
      "B":
        "answer": "Ignore fear as a factor and instead turn to logic to guide your
        decision?"
        "explanation": "Your brain is not afraid of fear! We all have a system that
        processes emotions within our brain. Fear is one of the main emotions processed in
        this system. One of your superpowers is the ability to suppress fear! You should
        also know that acknowledging and incorporating your fear can benefit your logical
        choices, so stay balanced and strong!"
  "question_10":
      "question": "We all have an uncanny ability to memorize information. Our brains have
      entire structures with the sole purpose of memorizing information. When memorizing
      information to study for a test/presentation, do you:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Focus your effort on the process and even though you might not be super
        interested in how the information is relevant to your life, you still consider it
        like a game and make it a fun process to memorize this information?"
        "explanation": "Your brain is like a muscle and it can grow with strategic effort!
        You like to learn new information and enjoy the process. This type of thinking will
        help you develop problem-solving skills that are creative and persevering."
      "B":
        "answer": "Focus your effort on the facts so you can do well on the test, but
        you're not super interested in how the information is relevant to your life."
        "explanation": "Memorizing facts builds certain structures of your brain!
        Literally, your memorization ability is growing structures within your brain.
        Getting a high five, or a pat on the back, isn't the end. You don't want that brain
        muscle to shrink as the knowledge seeps out your ear holes! Apply that new
        information in a fun way. This will keep that knowledge fresh and your brain plump!"
  "question_11":
      "question": "Life is stressful. The more we ask of ourselves, the more we -- and our
      brains -- are overcome with stress. When you feel stressed out, do you:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Suppress it and push it out of the way as much as possible, pushing it
        down to just deal with the stressful experience so you can be happy again once it's
        over."
        "explanation": "You head butt stress and push it out of the way! Suppressing stress
        can have different effects. It can amp up your performance in the present and have
        no effect later on. However, it can come back to bite you! So, be mindful that
        suppression may have some negative effects. Learning new strategies for stress
        management is easy."
      "B":
        "answer": "Feel the stress and look at it like an obstacle to get through – like
        another round of Jeopardy."
        "explanation": "It is well-known that emotions affect the way we feel.  Negative
        emotions, like stress, can really bring us down and negatively influence our
        performance. You likely characterize stress in a way that allows you to amp up your
        performance. Acknowledging and feeling the stress likely helps you take your game
        to the next level."
  "question_12":
      "question": "After a long day, it's often hard to get to sleep. People joke about
      counting sheep to get some z's. When I lay down to go to sleep, I:"
      "A":
        "answer": "Fall asleep as soon as my head hits the pillow."
        "explanation": "We all need sleep to consolidate memories, taking things we have
        learned during the day and incorporating them into our life. Your ability to easily
        fall asleep likely prepares your brain to incorporate new information! Keep the
        \"Zzzz's\" coming!"
      "B":
        "answer": "I spend hours on my phone, playing games and seeing what my friends are
        up to before I fall asleep."
        "explanation": "We all need sleep to consolidate memories and to take what we have
        learned during the day and incorporate it into our life. You are likely an
        efficient consolidator. We now know that not everyone needs 8 hours! You likely
        need much less to incorporate new information into your brain! But, be careful!
        Check in with yourself and don't always think that you can go non-stop."
